NYS PERB Agreements 5140
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Municipalities: Syracuse through Tonowanda (Box 353)
  - Tarrey Town (Box 353, Folder 5)
  - Tarry Town (Box 353, Folder 6)
  - Theresa (Box 353, Folder 7)
  - Theresa (Town) (Box 353, Folder 8)
  - Thurman (Box 353, Folder 9)
  - Tioga (Box 353, Folder 10)
  - Tonawanda (Box 353, Folder 11)
  - Tonawanda- Town (Box 353, Folder 12)
  - Tonawanda- Cities (Box 353, Folder 13)
  - Tonawanda (Box 353, Folder 14)
  - Tonawanda (Box 353, Folder 15)
- Municipalities: Toronto through Utica (Box 354)
  - Trenton (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - Triborough Bridge Authority (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - Town of Troupsburg (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Troy, city of (Box 354, Folder 4)
  - Troy (Box 354, Folder 5)
  - Tuckahoe (Box 354, Folder 6)
  - Tupper Lake (Box 354, Folder 7)
  - Tupper Lake, Village of (Box 354, Folder 8)
  - Tuscarora, Town (Box 354, Folder 9)
  - Tuxedo (Box 354, Folder 10)
  - Tuxedo (Box 354, Folder 11)
  - Ulster (Box 354, Folder 12)
  - Union (Box 354, Folder 13)
  - Union Town (Box 354, Folder 14)
  - Uniondale (Box 354, Folder 15)
  - Utica (Box 354, Folder 16)
  - Utica, City of (Box 354, Folder 17)
  - Utica (Box 354, Folder 18)
  - Utica, Cities (Box 354, Folder 19)
- Municipalities: Valley Stream through Waterloo (Box 355)
  - Valley Stream (Box 355, Folder 1)
  - Valley Stream (Village) (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - Valley Stream (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Van Buren, Town of (Box 355, Folder 4)
  - Verona (Box 355, Folder 5)
  - Verona (Box 355, Folder 6)
  - Vestal (Box 355, Folder 7)
  - Vienna, Town of (Box 355, Folder 8)
  - Waddington (Box 355, Folder 9)
  - Walden (Box 355, Folder 10)
  - Towns- Wallkill (Orange County) (Box 355, Folder 11)
  - Wallkill (Box 355, Folder 12)
  - Wallkill (Box 355, Folder 13)
  - Walton (town of) (Box 355, Folder 14)
  - Walton (Box 355, Folder 15)
  - Walton (Box 355, Folder 16)
  - Wantagh (Box 355, Folder 17)
  - Warrensburg (Town of) (Box 355, Folder 18)
  - Wantagh (Box 355, Folder 19)
  - Warrensburg (Box 355, Folder 20)
  - Warrensburg- Town of (Box 355, Folder 21)
  - Warwarsing (Box 355, Folder 22)
  - Warwick (Box 355, Folder 23)
  - Warwick, Town of (Box 355, Folder 24)
  - Warwick, Town (Box 355, Folder 25)
  - Warwick, Village (Box 355, Folder 26)
  - Washington (Box 355, Folder 27)
  - Washingtonville (Box 355, Folder 28)
  - Waterloo (Box 355, Folder 29)
  - Waterloo (Box 355, Folder 30)
- Municipalities: Watertown through Wellsville (Box 356)
  - Watertown, City of (Box 356, Folder 1)
  - Cities- Watertown (Box 356, Folder 2)
  - Watertown (Box 356, Folder 3)
  - Watertown (Box 356, Folder 4)
  - Watertown (Box 356, Folder 5)
  - Watertown (Box 356, Folder 6)
  - Watervliet (Box 356, Folder 7)
  - Watervliet (Box 356, Folder 8)
  - Watervliet- Cities (Box 356, Folder 9)
  - Watkins Glen- Village of (Box 356, Folder 10)
  - Watkins Glen (Box 356, Folder 11)
  - Watson (Box 356, Folder 12)
  - Watson (Box 356, Folder 13)
  - Waverly, Village (Box 356, Folder 14)
  - Waverly, Town (Box 356, Folder 15)
  - Waverly (Box 356, Folder 16)
  - Warwarsing, Town of (Box 356, Folder 17)
  - Wayne (Box 356, Folder 18)
  - Webster (Box 356, Folder 19)
  - Webster (Town) (Box 356, Folder 20)
  - Wellsville (Box 356, Folder 21)
  - Wellsville (Box 356, Folder 22)
  - Wellsville (Box 356, Folder 23)
- Municipalities: West Long Beach through West Union (Box 357)
  - West Long Beach (Box 357, Folder 1)
  - West Long Beach Sewer District- Other (Box 357, Folder 2)
  - West Seneca (Box 357, Folder 3)
  - Towns- West Seneca (Box 357, Folder 4)
  - West Seneca (Box 357, Folder 5)
  - Westbury (Box 357, Folder 6)
  - Westbury (Box 357, Folder 7)
  - Westbury (Village) (Box 357, Folder 8)
  - Westchester JT. Waterworks- Other (Box 357, Folder 9)
  - Western Regional OTB (Box 357, Folder 10)
  - Western Region (Box 357, Folder 11)
  - Westfield (Box 357, Folder 12)
  - Westfield Villages (Box 357, Folder 13)
  - Westfield (Village of) (Box 357, Folder 14)
  - Westfield (Box 357, Folder 15)
  - Westhampton Beach (Box 357, Folder 16)
  - Town of Westport (Box 357, Folder 17)
  - Westport, Town of (Box 357, Folder 18)
  - West Union Town (Box 357, Folder 19)
- Municipalities: White Creek through Woodridge (Box 358)
  - White Creek (Box 358, Folder 1)
  - White Plains (Box 358, Folder 2)
  - White Plains (City of) (Box 358, Folder 3)
  - White Plains (Box 358, Folder 4)
  - Williamson and AFSCME #1635G (Box 358, Folder 5)
  - Williamson (Box 358, Folder 6)
  - Williamsville, Village of (Box 358, Folder 7)
  - Williamsville (Village) (Box 358, Folder 8)
  - Williston Park (Box 358, Folder 9)
  - Wilna (Box 358, Folder 10)
  - Windsor (Box 358, Folder 11)
  - Village of Woodridge (Box 358, Folder 12)
- Municipalities: Yates through Yorkville (Box 359)
  - Yates (Box 359, Folder 1)
  - Yates (Box 359, Folder 2)
  - Yonkers, City of (Box 359, Folder 3)
  - Yonkers (City) (Box 359, Folder 4)
  - Yonkers (Box 359, Folder 5)
  - Yorktown (Box 359, Folder 6)
  - Yorktown (Box 359, Folder 7)
  - Yorkville (Box 359, Folder 8)
- Counties: Adirondack through Allegany (Box 360)
  - Adirondack (Box 360, Folder 1)
  - Albany (Box 360, Folder 2)
  - Albany County (Box 360, Folder 3)
  - Albany (Box 360, Folder 4)
  - Allegany (County of) (Box 360, Folder 5)
  - Allegany County (Box 360, Folder 6)
  - Allegany, County of (Box 360, Folder 7)
  - Allegany County (Box 360, Folder 8)
  - Allegany (Box 360, Folder 9)
- Counties: Broome through Broome (Box 361)
  - Broome County- Most Current Contracts (Box 361, Folder 1)
  - Broome (Box 361, Folder 2)
  - Broome County (Box 361, Folder 3)
  - Broome (Box 361, Folder 4)
  - Broome, County of (Box 361, Folder 5)
  - Broome (Box 361, Folder 6)
  - Buffalo and Erie County (Box 361, Folder 7)
- Counties: Buffalo-Erie through Chatouqua (Box 362)
  - Buffalo and Erie County (Box 362, Folder 1)
  - Buffalo and Erie County (Box 362, Folder 2)
  - Syracuse I (Box 362, Folder 3)
  - Cattaraugus County (Box 362, Folder 4)
  - Cattaraugus- Counties (Box 362, Folder 5)
  - Cattaraugus, County of (Box 362, Folder 6)
  - Cattaraugus (Box 362, Folder 7)
  - Cattaraugus County (Box 362, Folder 8)
  - Cattaraugus, County of (Box 362, Folder 9)
  - Cayuga County (Box 362, Folder 10)
  - Cayuga County (Box 362, Folder 11)
  - Cayuga (Box 362, Folder 12)
  - Cayuga, County of (Box 362, Folder 13)
  - Chatham (Box 362, Folder 14)
  - Chautauqua County (Box 362, Folder 15)
  - Chautauqua, County of (Box 362, Folder 16)
  - Chautauqua County (Box 362, Folder 17)
- Counties: Chemung through Clinton (Box 363)
  - Chemung County (Box 363, Folder 1)
  - Counties-Chemung (Box 363, Folder 2)
  - Chemung (Box 363, Folder 3)
  - Chemung County (Box 363, Folder 4)
  - Chemung County (Box 363, Folder 5)
  - Chenango (Box 363, Folder 6)
  - Chenango, County of (Box 363, Folder 7)
  - Chenango (Box 363, Folder 8)
  - Chenango, County of (Box 363, Folder 9)
  - Clinton County (Box 363, Folder 10)
  - Clinton (Box 363, Folder 11)
  - Clinton County (Box 363, Folder 12)
- Counties: Columbia through Delaware (Box 364)
  - Columbia County (Box 364, Folder 1)
  - Columbia County (Box 364, Folder 2)
  - Columbia County (Box 364, Folder 3)
  - Corning (Box 364, Folder 4)
  - Cortland (Box 364, Folder 5)
  - Cortland County (Box 364, Folder 6)
  - Cortland County (Box 364, Folder 7)
  - Delaware- Counties (Box 364, Folder 8)
  - Delaware (Box 364, Folder 9)
  - Delaware (Box 364, Folder 10)
  - Delaware County (Box 364, Folder 11)
  - Delaware (Box 364, Folder 12)
- Counties: Dutchess through Erie (Box 365)
  - Dutchess County (Box 365, Folder 1)
  - Counties- Dutchess (Box 365, Folder 2)
  - Dutchess County (Box 365, Folder 3)
  - Dutchess County (Box 365, Folder 4)
  - Erie County (Box 365, Folder 5)
  - Counties- Erie (Box 365, Folder 6)
  - Erie County (Box 365, Folder 7)
- Counties: Erie through Franklin (Box 366)
  - Erie (Box 366, Folder 1)
  - Erie County (Box 366, Folder 2)
  - Essex County (Box 366, Folder 3)
  - Counties- Essex (Box 366, Folder 4)
  - Essex, County of (Box 366, Folder 5)
  - Franklin, County of (Box 366, Folder 6)
  - Franklin, Counties (Box 366, Folder 7)
  - Franklin (Box 366, Folder 8)
- Counties: Fulton through Greene (Box 367)
  - Fulton County (Box 367, Folder 1)
  - Fulton County (Box 367, Folder 2)
  - Fulton County (Box 367, Folder 3)
  - Genesee, County of (Box 367, Folder 4)
  - Genesee- Counties (Box 367, Folder 5)
  - Genesee (Box 367, Folder 6)
  - Genesee Counties (Box 367, Folder 7)
  - Genesee (Box 367, Folder 8)
  - Greene County (Box 367, Folder 9)
  - Greene- Counties (Box 367, Folder 10)
  - Greene (Box 367, Folder 11)
- Counties: Herkimer through Livingston (Box 368)
  - Greene (Box 368, Folder 1)
  - Herkimer, County of (Box 368, Folder 2)
  - Herkimer (Box 368, Folder 3)
  - Herkimer County (Box 368, Folder 4)
  - Herkimer (Box 368, Folder 5)
  - Herkimer (Box 368, Folder 6)
  - Jefferson Couty (Box 368, Folder 7)
  - Jefferson County (Box 368, Folder 8)
  - Jefferson (Box 368, Folder 9)
  - Lewis County (Box 368, Folder 10)
  - Lewis- Counties (Box 368, Folder 11)
  - Lewis (Box 368, Folder 12)
  - Livingston County (Box 368, Folder 13)
  - Livingston (Box 368, Folder 14)
  - Livingston- County of (Box 368, Folder 15)
  - County of Livingston (Box 368, Folder 16)
- Counties: Madison through Montgomery (Box 369)
  - Madison County (Box 369, Folder 1)
  - Madison (Box 369, Folder 2)
  - Madison County (Box 369, Folder 3)
  - Madison County (Box 369, Folder 4)
  - Counties- Monroe (Box 369, Folder 5)
  - Monroe County (Box 369, Folder 6)
  - Monroe County (Box 369, Folder 7)
  - Monroe, County of (Box 369, Folder 8)
  - Monroe (Box 369, Folder 9)
  - Montgomery (Box 369, Folder 10)
  - Montgomery County (Box 369, Folder 11)
  - Montgomery (Box 369, Folder 12)
  - Montgomery, County of (Box 369, Folder 13)
- Counties: Nassau through Niagara (Box 370)
  - Nassau County (Box 370, Folder 1)
  - Nassau County (Box 370, Folder 2)
  - Nassau County (Box 370, Folder 3)
  - Niagara County (Box 370, Folder 4)
  - Niagara (Box 370, Folder 5)
  - Niagara County (Box 370, Folder 6)
  - Niagara (Box 370, Folder 7)
- Counties: Oneida through Onondaga (Box 371)
  - Oneida, County of (Box 371, Folder 1)
  - Oneida County (Box 371, Folder 2)
  - Oneida- Counties (Box 371, Folder 3)
  - Oneida (Box 371, Folder 4)
  - Onondaga County (Box 371, Folder 5)
  - Onondaga, County of (Box 371, Folder 6)
  - Onondaga County (Box 371, Folder 7)
  - Onondaga (Box 371, Folder 8)
  - Onondaga County (Box 371, Folder 9)
- Counties: Ontario through Oswego (Box 372)
  - Ontario (Box 372, Folder 1)
  - Ontario (Box 372, Folder 2)
  - Ontario (Box 372, Folder 3)
  - Orange County (Box 372, Folder 4)
  - Orange County (Box 372, Folder 5)
  - Orleans, County of (Box 372, Folder 6)
  - Orleans County (Box 372, Folder 7)
  - Counties- Orleans (Box 372, Folder 8)
  - Orleans (Box 372, Folder 9)
  - Oswego, County of (Box 372, Folder 10)
  - Oswego County (Box 372, Folder 11)
- Counties: Oswego through Rensselaer (Box 373)
  - Oswego (Box 373, Folder 1)
  - Oswego (Box 373, Folder 2)
  - Otsego (Box 373, Folder 3)
  - Otsego (Box 373, Folder 4)
  - Otsego County (Box 373, Folder 5)
  - Otsego (Box 373, Folder 6)
  - Putnam County (Box 373, Folder 7)
  - Putnam County (Box 373, Folder 8)
  - Putnam (Box 373, Folder 9)
  - Putnam, County of (Box 373, Folder 10)
  - Rensselaer County (Box 373, Folder 11)
  - Counties- Rensselaer Bd. Of Supervisors (Box 373, Folder 12)
- Counties: Rockland through Rockland (Box 374)
  - Rockland (Box 374, Folder 1)
  - Rockland, County of (Box 374, Folder 2)
  - Rockland- County (Box 374, Folder 3)
  - Rockland County (Box 374, Folder 4)
  - Rockland (Box 374, Folder 5)
  - Rockland County (Box 374, Folder 6)
- Counties: St. Lawrence through Schenectady (Box 375)
  - St. Lawrence County (Box 375, Folder 1)
  - St. Lawrence (Box 375, Folder 2)
  - Saint Lawrence, County of (Box 375, Folder 3)
  - St. Lawrence (Box 375, Folder 4)
  - St. Lawrence (Box 375, Folder 5)
  - Saratoga County (Box 375, Folder 6)
  - Saratoga County (Box 375, Folder 7)
  - Saratoga County (Box 375, Folder 8)
  - Saratoga (Box 375, Folder 9)
  - Saratoga County (Box 375, Folder 10)
  - Schenectady, County of (Box 375, Folder 11)
  - Schenectady, Counties (Box 375, Folder 12)
  - Schenectady (Box 375, Folder 13)
- Counties: Schoharie through Steuben (Box 376)
  - Schoharie County (Box 376, Folder 1)
  - Schuyler County (Box 376, Folder 2)
  - Schoharie- Counties (Box 376, Folder 3)
  - Schoharie (Box 376, Folder 4)
  - Schoharie (Box 376, Folder 5)
  - Schuyler County (Box 376, Folder 6)
  - Seneca (Box 376, Folder 7)
  - Seneca (Box 376, Folder 8)
  - Seneca (Box 376, Folder 9)
  - Seneca County (Box 376, Folder 10)
  - Steuben County (Box 376, Folder 11)
  - Steuben (Box 376, Folder 12)
  - Steuben (Box 376, Folder 13)
  - Steuben County (Box 376, Folder 14)
  - Steuben (Box 376, Folder 15)
- Counties: Suffolk through Sullivan (Box 377)
  - Suffolk County (Box 377, Folder 1)
  - Suffolk County Water Authority (Box 377, Folder 2)
  - Suffolk- County (Box 377, Folder 3)
  - Suffolk, County of (Box 377, Folder 4)
  - Suffolk (Box 377, Folder 5)
  - Sullivan (Box 377, Folder 6)
  - Sullivan County (Box 377, Folder 7)
  - Sullivan- Counties (Box 377, Folder 8)
  - Sullivan County (Box 377, Folder 9)
  - Sullivan County (Box 377, Folder 10)
- Counties: Tioga through Warrensburgh (Box 378)
  - Tioga County (Box 378, Folder 1)
  - Tioga (Box 378, Folder 2)
  - Tioga, County of (Box 378, Folder 3)
  - Tioga- Counties (Box 378, Folder 4)
  - Tioga (County) (Box 378, Folder 5)
  - Tioga (Box 378, Folder 6)
  - Tompkins (Box 378, Folder 7)
  - Counties- Tompkins (Box 378, Folder 8)
  - Tompkins County (Box 378, Folder 9)
  - Tompkins, County of (Box 378, Folder 10)
  - Tompkins (Box 378, Folder 11)
  - Ulster (Box 378, Folder 12)
  - Ulster (Box 378, Folder 13)
  - Ulster, County of (Box 378, Folder 14)
  - Ulster- Counties (Box 378, Folder 15)
  - Warren County (Box 378, Folder 16)
  - Warren (Box 378, Folder 17)
  - Warren (Box 378, Folder 18)
  - Counties- Warren (Box 378, Folder 19)
  - Washington County (Box 378, Folder 20)
  - Wayne County (Box 378, Folder 21)
- Counties: Washington through Westchester (Box 379)
  - Washington County Highway Dept. (Box 379, Folder 1)
  - Washington County (Box 379, Folder 2)
  - Washington County (Box 379, Folder 3)
  - Washington (Box 379, Folder 4)
  - Wayne County (Box 379, Folder 5)
  - County of Wayne (Box 379, Folder 6)
  - Wayne, County of (Box 379, Folder 7)
  - Wayne (Box 379, Folder 8)
  - Wayne (Box 379, Folder 9)
  - Westchester (Box 379, Folder 10)
  - Westchester- Counties (Box 379, Folder 11)
- Counties: Westchester through Yates (Box 380)
  - Westchester (Box 380, Folder 1)
  - Westchester, County of (Box 380, Folder 2)
  - Westchester County (Box 380, Folder 3)
  - Wyoming County (Box 380, Folder 4)
  - Wyoming County (Box 380, Folder 5)
  - Wyoming (Box 380, Folder 6)
  - Counties- Wyoming (Box 380, Folder 7)
  - Yates (Box 380, Folder 8)
  - Yates- Counties (Box 380, Folder 9)
  - Yates County (Box 380, Folder 10)
  - Yates (Box 380, Folder 11)
- New York State: Building Authority through NYS Admin. Bd. Of Judicial Conference (Box 381)
  - Batavia Bus Service (Box 381, Folder 1)
  - Bridge Authority (Box 381, Folder 2)
  - Bridge Authority (Box 381, Folder 3)
  - Bridge Authority (Box 381, Folder 4)
  - NYS Canal Corporation- PEF (Box 381, Folder 5)
  - Capital District Transit System (Box 381, Folder 6)
  - Capital District Off-Track Betting (Box 381, Folder 7)
  - Dormitory Authority (Box 381, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Facilities Corporation (Box 381, Folder 9)
  - Electric and Gas Corporation (Box 381, Folder 10)
  - General Services (Box 381, Folder 11)
  - Health Research Inc. (Box 381, Folder 12)
  - Higher Education Assistance Corporation (Box 381, Folder 13)
  - Housing Finance Agency (Box 381, Folder 14)
  - Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority (Box 381, Folder 15)
  - Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority (Box 381, Folder 16)
  - Nassau Regional Off-Track Betting (Box 381, Folder 17)
  - New York and New Jersey Port Authority and Port Authority PBA (Box 381, Folder 18)
  - New York State Administrative Board of Judicial Conference (Box 381, Folder 19)
- New York State: NYS Admin. Services through NYS Senate Professional Assn. (Box 382)
  - New York State- Administrative Services Unit (Box 382, Folder 1)
  - New York State- CSEA Division of Military and Naval Affairs (Box 382, Folder 2)
  - New York State- Institutional Services Unit (Box 382, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Services Unit- CSEA (Box 382, Folder 4)
  - New York State- Operational Services Unit (Box 382, Folder 5)
  - CSEA Operation Services Unit (Box 382, Folder 6)
  - New York State- Palisades Interstate Park (Box 382, Folder 7)
  - New York State- Professional, Scientific and Technical Services Unit (Box 382, Folder 8)
  - New York State- Security Services Unit (Box 382, Folder 9)
  - NY- AFSCME DC S2 (Box 382, Folder 10)
  - New York State- Security Supervisors Unit (Box 382, Folder 11)
  - New York State- Senate Professional Association (Box 382, Folder 12)
- New York State: NYS United University Professors through Thruway Authority (Box 383)
  - New York State- United University Professions (Box 383, Folder 1)
  - New York State of & United University Professions 1995-1999 (Box 383, Folder 2)
  - New York State of & United University Professions 1999-2003 (Box 383, Folder 3)
  - New York State of & United University Professions1982-1985 (Box 383, Folder 4)
  - New York State Nurses Association 1984-1987 (Box 383, Folder 5)
  - New York State of Triborough & Tunnel Authority (Box 383, Folder 6)
  - Niagara Frontier Transit Metro System, Inc. (Box 383, Folder 7)
  - Olympic Regional Development Authority (Box 383, Folder 8)
  - Power Authority (Box 383, Folder 9)
  - Power Authority (Box 383, Folder 10)
  - New York State- Public Employees Federation (Box 383, Folder 11)
  - NYS Rent Regulation Services AFSCME Council 37 (Box 383, Folder 12)
  - New York State of & Security Unit Employees Council 82, 1979-1982 (Box 383, Folder 13)
  - Suffolk Regional Off-Track Betting (Box 383, Folder 14)
  - Teacher's Retirement System (Box 383, Folder 15)
  - Thruway Authority (Box 383, Folder 16)
  - Thruway Authority (Box 383, Folder 17)
  - Thruway Authority (Box 383, Folder 18)
  - Thruway Authority (Box 383, Folder 19)
  - Thruway Authority (Box 383, Folder 20)
  - Thruway Authority (Box 383, Folder 21)
  - Thruway Authority (Box 383, Folder 22)
- New York State: Thruway Authority through University Construction Fund (Box 384)
  - Thruway Authority (Box 384, Folder 1)
  - Thruway Authority (Box 384, Folder 2)
  - Thruway Authority (Box 384, Folder 3)
  - NYS Thruway Authority (Box 384, Folder 4)
  - NYC Transit (Box 384, Folder 5)
  - NYC Transit Authority (Box 384, Folder 6)
  - NYC Transit Authority and Communications Workers of America (Box 384, Folder 7)
  - NYC Transit Authority and Endowments (Box 384, Folder 8)
  - NYC Transit Auth. and Special Inspectors Benevolent Assn. (Box 384, Folder 9)
  - NYC Transit Auth. And Special Inspectors Benevolent Assn. (Box 384, Folder 10)
  - State University Construction Fund (Box 384, Folder 11)
- New York State: Unified Court System through Unified Courth System (Box 385)
  - Unified Court System (Box 385, Folder 1)
  - Unified Court System (Box 385, Folder 2)
  - Unified Court System (Box 385, Folder 3)
  - Unified Court System (Box 385, Folder 4)
  - Unified Court System (Box 385, Folder 5)
  - Unified Court System (Box 385, Folder 6)
  - Unified Court System (Box 385, Folder 7)
  - Unified Court System (Box 385, Folder 8)
  - Unified Court System (Box 385, Folder 9)
  - Unified Court System (Box 385, Folder 10)
- New York State: Unified Court System through Western Regional Off-Track Betting (Box 386)
  - Unified Court System (Box 386, Folder 1)
  - Unified Court System (Box 386, Folder 2)
  - Thruway Authority (Box 386, Folder 3)
  - Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority (Box 386, Folder 4)
  - Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority (Box 386, Folder 5)
  - Western Regional Off-Track Betting (Box 386, Folder 6)
  - Western Regional Off-Track Betting (Box 386, Folder 7)
- New York State Fact Finding: Police and Firemen: Albany through Johnson City (Box 387)
  - Adirondack (Box 387, Folder 1)
  - Albany (Box 387, Folder 2)
  - Alden, Town of (Box 387, Folder 3)
  - Amsterdam, City of (Box 387, Folder 4)
  - Amherst, Town of (Box 387, Folder 5)
  - Auburn, City of (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Babylon, Town of (Box 387, Folder 7)
  - Barre, Town of (Box 387, Folder 8)
  - Batavia, City of (Box 387, Folder 9)
  - Beacon, City of (Box 387, Folder 10)
  - Beekman (Box 387, Folder 11)
  - Bethel, Town of (Box 387, Folder 12)
  - Binghamton, City of (Box 387, Folder 13)
  - Binghamton, Johnson City (Box 387, Folder 14)
  - Brookhaven, Town of (Box 387, Folder 15)
  - Buffalo, City of (Box 387, Folder 16)
  - Calicoon, City of (Box 387, Folder 17)
  - Cameron, Town of (Box 387, Folder 18)
  - Canton, City of (Box 387, Folder 19)
  - Canajoharie (Box 387, Folder 20)
  - Candor, Town of (Box 387, Folder 21)
  - Carmel, Town of (Box 387, Folder 22)
  - Cheektowaga, Town of (Box 387, Folder 23)
  - Clarkstown, Town of (Box 387, Folder 24)
  - Cohoes (Box 387, Folder 25)
  - Colton, Town of (Box 387, Folder 26)
  - Corning, City of (Box 387, Folder 27)
  - Cornwall (Box 387, Folder 28)
  - Croton-on-Hudson, City of (Box 387, Folder 29)
  - Dansville, Village of (Box 387, Folder 30)
  - Davenport, Town of (Box 387, Folder 31)
  - Depew, Village of (Box 387, Folder 32)
  - Eastchester, Town of (Box 387, Folder 33)
  - Ellenville (Box 387, Folder 34)
  - Elmira City (Box 387, Folder 35)
  - Endicott, Village of (Box 387, Folder 36)
  - Evans, Town of (Box 387, Folder 37)
  - Fallsburg, Town of (Box 387, Folder 38)
  - Frankfurt, Village of (Box 387, Folder 39)
  - Fredonia, Town of (Box 387, Folder 40)
  - Free Port (Box 387, Folder 41)
  - Fremont, Town of (Box 387, Folder 42)
  - Fulton (Box 387, Folder 43)
  - Garden City, Village (Box 387, Folder 44)
  - Geneseo, Village of (Box 387, Folder 45)
  - Geneva, City of (Box 387, Folder 46)
  - Glen Cove, City of (Box 387, Folder 47)
  - Glenville, Town of (Box 387, Folder 48)
  - Gloversville (Box 387, Folder 49)
  - Gloversville- Johnstown (Box 387, Folder 50)
  - Goshen, Village of (Box 387, Folder 51)
  - Gouverneur, Town of (Box 387, Folder 52)
  - Gowanda, Village of (Box 387, Folder 53)
  - Greece, Town of (Box 387, Folder 54)
  - Greenburgh, Town of (Box 387, Folder 55)
  - Hamburg, Town of (Box 387, Folder 56)
  - Harrison, Town of (Box 387, Folder 57)
  - Hastings-on-the-Hudson (Box 387, Folder 58)
  - Henrietta, Town of (Box 387, Folder 59)
  - Hornell (Box 387, Folder 60)
  - Hudson, City of (Box 387, Folder 61)
  - Huntington, Town of (Box 387, Folder 62)
  - Kion, Village of (Box 387, Folder 63)
  - Irondequoit, Town of (Box 387, Folder 64)
  - Islip, Town of (Box 387, Folder 65)
  - Ithaca, City of (Box 387, Folder 66)
  - Jamestown, City of (Box 387, Folder 67)
  - Johnson City, Village of (Box 387, Folder 68)
- New York State Fact Finding: Police and Firemen: Kenmore through Yorktown (Box 388)
  - Kenmore, Village of (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Kent, Town of (Box 388, Folder 2)
  - Kingston (Box 388, Folder 3)
  - Kortright (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Lackawanna (City of) (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - Lake Placid, Village of (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Lake Success (Box 388, Folder 7)
  - Larchmont, Village of (Box 388, Folder 8)
  - Lindenhurst, Village of (Box 388, Folder 9)
  - Little Falls, City of (Box 388, Folder 10)
  - Lockport, City of (Box 388, Folder 11)
  - Lockport Memorial Hospital (Box 388, Folder 12)